Redmond, where are you crawling to?
Severin, you, uh...
you need something?
I’m thinking of
erasing House Carter completely.
What do you think?
Of course, if you have any objections,
I can erase you too.
That… that won’t be necessary.
Severin, you carry Carter blood!
You should help the family!
Carter blood?
Funny. You didn't mention that
when you threw us out.
I was wrong.
I'll sign the entire house over to you
right now.
You are the only heir!
Just save us!
You think I give
a shit about that?
The moment you chose Redmond,
you signed House Carter’s death warrant.
Send word across the Sovereign Sanctum.
Within fifteen minutes,
I want
House Carter erased from Golantis.
As you command!
Severin, don't do this!
Go rot in hell
with your golden boy and your
snake of a wife.
No!
Severin.
He's your father!
- I never forgive those who have hurt me.
- Please，
save him!
No matter who they are.
Guards!
Throw them out!
Can it be lighter?
Godfather!
Please!
I didn't know!
You loved torturing the
people beneath you, Jeyn.
Let's see how
you like the executioner.
Cassia, take him out.
Standard execution.
Yes, my lord!
Please, Godfather!
- Forgive us!
You all called my miner brothers "filth".
Since that's
how you feel,
your titles, lands, and wealth
will be stripped and confiscated.